<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<MD_Metadata xmlns="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/gmd" xmlns:gco="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/gco" xmlns:gts="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/gts" xmlns:srv="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/srv" xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <fileIdentifier>
    <gco:CharacterString>juncbvnbijmmu6d</gco:CharacterString>
  </fileIdentifier>
  <language>
    <LanguageCode codeList="http://www.loc.gov/standards/iso639-2/php/code_list.php" codeListValue="eng" codeSpace="ISO639-2">eng</LanguageCode>
  </language>
  <characterSet>
    <MD_CharacterSetCode codeList="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/resources/Codelist/gmxCodelists.xml#MD_CharacterSetCode" codeListValue="utf8" codeSpace="ISOTC211/19115">utf8</MD_CharacterSetCode>
  </characterSet>
  <hierarchyLevel>
    <MD_ScopeCode codeList="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/resources/Codelist/gmxCodelists.xml#MD_ScopeCode" codeListValue="dataset" codeSpace="ISOTC211/19115">dataset</MD_ScopeCode>
  </hierarchyLevel>
  <contact>
    <CI_ResponsibleParty>
      <organisationName>
        <gco:CharacterString>4 Earth Intelligence Ltd</gco:CharacterString>
      </organisationName>
      <contactInfo>
        <CI_Contact>
          <address>
            <CI_Address>
              <deliveryPoint>
                <gco:CharacterString>Unit 1, Kings Court, Little King Street</gco:CharacterString>
              </deliveryPoint>
              <city>
                <gco:CharacterString>Bristol</gco:CharacterString>
              </city>
              <administrativeArea>
                <gco:CharacterString>City of Bristol</gco:CharacterString>
              </administrativeArea>
              <postalCode>
                <gco:CharacterString>BS1 4HW</gco:CharacterString>
              </postalCode>
              <country>
                <Country codeList="http://www.iso.org/iso/country_codes/iso_3166_code_lists.htm" codeListValue="GB" codeSpace="ISO3166-1">GB</Country>
              </country>
              <electronicMailAddress>
                <gco:CharacterString>info@4earthintelligence.com</gco:CharacterString>
              </electronicMailAddress>
            </CI_Address>
          </address>
        </CI_Contact>
      </contactInfo>
      <role>
        <CI_RoleCode codeList="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/resources/Codelist/gmxCodelists.xml#CI_RoleCode" codeListValue="custodian" codeSpace="ISOTC211/19115">custodian
distributor
pointofcontact</CI_RoleCode>
      </role>
    </CI_ResponsibleParty>
  </contact>
  <dateStamp>
    <gco:Date>27/01/2020</gco:Date>
  </dateStamp>
  <metadataStandardName>
    <gco:CharacterString>NAP - Metadata</gco:CharacterString>
  </metadataStandardName>
  <metadataStandardVersion>
    <gco:CharacterString>1.2</gco:CharacterString>
  </metadataStandardVersion>
  <referenceSystemInfo>
    <MD_ReferenceSystem>
      <referenceSystemIdentifier>
        <RS_Identifier>
          <code>
            <gco:CharacterString>British National Grid</gco:CharacterString>
          </code>
        </RS_Identifier>
      </referenceSystemIdentifier>
    </MD_ReferenceSystem>
  </referenceSystemInfo>
  <referenceSystemInfo>
    <MD_ReferenceSystem>
      <referenceSystemIdentifier>
        <RS_Identifier>
          <code>
            <gco:CharacterString>OSGB 1936</gco:CharacterString>
          </code>
        </RS_Identifier>
      </referenceSystemIdentifier>
    </MD_ReferenceSystem>
  </referenceSystemInfo>
  <identificationInfo>
    <MD_DataIdentification>
      <citation>
        <CI_Citation>
          <title>
            <gco:CharacterString>S2_LULC_20190919_London_OSGB_BNG</gco:CharacterString>
          </title>
          <date>
            <CI_Date>
              <date>
                <gco:Date>24/01/2020</gco:Date>
              </date>
              <dateType>
                <CI_DateTypeCode codeList="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/resources/Codelist/gmxCodelists.xml#CI_DateTypeCode" codeListValue="creation" codeSpace="ISOTC211/19115">creation</CI_DateTypeCode>
              </dateType>
            </CI_Date>
          </date>
          <presentationForm>
            <CI_PresentationFormCode codeList="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/resources/Codelist/gmxCodelists.xml#CI_PresentationFormCode" codeListValue="documentDigital" codeSpace="ISOTC211/19115">documentDigital</CI_PresentationFormCode>
          </presentationForm>
        </CI_Citation>
      </citation>
      <summary>
        <gco:CharacterString>Satellite Derived Land Cover (LC) dataset.
Sensor: Sentinel 2
MMU: 400 sq m
Scale: 1:25,000
Coordinate System: British National Grid (EPSG:27700)
Schema: Adapted from CORINE Land Cover, Copyright 4 Earth Intelligence Ltd
File Type: ESRI Shapefile
</gco:CharacterString>
      </summary>
      <abstract>
        <gco:CharacterString>Satellite Derived Land Cover (LC) data can be created on either an image by image basis or from a mosaic of images that are close in date. The schema used is adapted from CORINE Land Cover. Land cover is delivered as ESRI Shapefiles named after the location, sensor, acquisition date, product and the horizontal reference system of the data.</gco:CharacterString>
      </abstract>
      <credit>
        <gco:CharacterString>4 Earth Intelligence; http://www.4earthintelligence.com</gco:CharacterString>
      </credit>
      <status>
        <MD_ProgressCode codeList="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/resources/Codelist/gmxCodelists.xml#MD_ProgressCode" codeListValue="completed" codeSpace="ISOTC211/19115">completed</MD_ProgressCode>
      </status>
      <resourceMaintenance>
        <MD_MaintenanceInformation>
          <maintenanceAndUpdateFrequency>
            <MD_MaintenanceFrequencyCode codeList="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/resources/Codelist/gmxCodelists.xml#MD_MaintenanceFrequencyCode" codeListValue="asNeeded" codeSpace="ISOTC211/19115">asNeeded</MD_MaintenanceFrequencyCode>
          </maintenanceAndUpdateFrequency>
        </MD_MaintenanceInformation>
      </resourceMaintenance>
      <descriptiveKeywords>
        <MD_Keywords>
          <keyword>
            <gco:CharacterString>Other Documents</gco:CharacterString>
          </keyword>
          <thesaurusName uuidref="723f6998-058e-11dc-8314-0800200c9a66" />
        </MD_Keywords>
      </descriptiveKeywords>
      <resourceConstraints>
        <MD_Constraints>
			<useLimitation>
				<gco:CharacterString>Only to be used for data evaluation</gco:CharacterString>
			  </useLimitation>
			</MD_Constraints>
		  </resourceConstraints>
		  <resourceConstraints>
			<MD_LegalConstraints>
			  <useLimitation>
				<gco:CharacterString>4 Earth Intelligence Data Evaluation License

	IMPORTANT: By accessing this data the Licensee confirms that they have read and agree to be legally bound by the following terms and conditions (the “Licence”). Please read these terms and conditions carefully. 

	1. Basis of Contract and Grant of Licence 
	1.1 The terms and conditions of this Licence govern the relationship between 4 Earth Intelligence Ltd, a company registered in United Kingdom under number 6002418 whose registered office is at Unit 1, King's Court, Little King Street, Bristol, BS1 4HW, UK (“4EI”) and The person, organisation or company who is accessing the Product, on the basis of these License terms (“Licensee”) when Licensee has access and use the sample data provided to them with this licence (the "Data"). 
	1.2 4EI hereby grants Licensee  a personal, non-transferable, non-exclusive licence for Licensee  and its employees to use the Data for a period of six (6) months only from the date of delivery ("Evaluation Period") to use the Data solely to the extent necessary for the internal evaluation and testing of the Data to ensure the Data is capable of being used under licence as part of their products or services, subject always to their compliance with Clause 3. Licensee shall not modify, adapt or merge the Data without first obtaining 4EI's prior written consent. 
	1.3 This Licence shall terminate automatically without notice on expiry of the Evaluation Period. During the Evaluation Period, 4EI may terminate this Licence immediately by giving Licensee written notice at any time. 
	1.4 Immediately following the expiry or earlier termination of this Licence, Licensee shall destroy or delete all copies of the Data which it holds or at 4EI's request return all copies of the Data to 4EI. In either case, Licensee shall provide, at 4EI’s request, a sworn statement by a duly authorised executive that Licensee no longer hold any of the Data. 

	2. Ownership 
	2.1 4EI or its suppliers own the intellectual property rights in the Data. All Data licensed to Licensee under this Licence remains the property of 4EI or its suppliers. 

	3. Licensee ’s obligations 
	3.1 Except as otherwise granted in this Licence, Licensee have no other rights in the use of the Data or any of 4EI's trademarks. Licensee  shall not: (i) use the Data for any activity within its business or organisation which is not directly related to the evaluation or testing the Data; (ii) pass any of the Data to any third party not directly involved in the evaluation or testing; (iii) use the Data to recreate any of 4EI's products, any part of such products or any similar or substantially equivalent products; or (iv) commercially exploit, sell, license or distribute the Data or any products or services incorporating the Data. 
	3.2 Licensee will effect and maintain technological and security measures to ensure that all Data is physically and electronically secure from unauthorised use or access. 
	3.3 Licensee will ensure that it fully protects the intellectual property rights in the Data and that it will not interfere with, alter or amend any of 4EI’s trade names and trademarks or other intellectual property or notices. Licensee will notify 4EI as soon as it suspects any infringement or any other breach by a third party of these intellectual property rights. 4EI shall, for the avoidance of doubt have sole conduct of any claim relating to intellectual property, and Licensee agree to give 4EI all reasonable assistance in pursuing any infringement. 

	4. Liability 
	4.1 Nothing in this Licence shall exclude or limit the liability of either party for death and personal injury caused by its negligence or for fraud. 
	4.2 Licensee acknowledge and agree that the Data is provided on an "as is" basis. 4EI does not give any warranty, representation or guarantee to the accuracy, suitability, reliability, completeness, performance, satisfactory quality, fitness for a particular purpose, in relation to the Data. 
	4.3 Subject to Clause 4.1, neither party shall be liable to the other in contract, tort or otherwise for:(i) any special, indirect or consequential losses or damages;(ii) any direct or indirect loss of profit, loss of business, loss of contracts, loss of data, loss of revenues or loss of anticipated savings or for any increased costs or expenses; or (iii) any direct losses and/or damages which in aggregate exceed £1000. 

	5. Confidentiality 
	5.1 The parties to this Licence will take all reasonable steps to ensure that any material or information identified by either party to be confidential (“Confidential Information”) which the other party has possession or knowledge of in connection with this Licence, will not be disclosed to others, in whole or in part, without the prior written permission of the other party. Neither party will have the obligation to maintain the confidentiality of any data or information which (i) was in the receiving party’s lawful possession prior to receipt from the other party (ii) is later lawfully obtained by the receiving party from a third party having no obligation of confidentiality to the other party (iii) is available to the public through no act or failure of the receiving party (iv) is readily available in the public domain or (v) is independently developed by the receiving party. 

	6. General 
	6.1 If any provision contained in this Licence shall be held to be invalid, unlawful or unenforceable to any extent, such term, condition or provision shall not affect the validity, legality or enforceability of the remainder of this Licence. 
	6.2 In no event will any delay, failure or omission (in whole or in part) in enforcing, exercising or pursuing any right, power, privilege, claim or remedy arising under this Licence or by law, be deemed to be or construed as a waiver, or bar to the enforcement, of that or any other right, power, privilege, claim or remedy in respect of the circumstances in question. 
	6.3 This Licence constitutes the entire agreement and understanding of the parties and supersedes any previous agreement or arrangement between the parties relating to the subject matter of this Licence. In entering into this Licence, the parties have not relied on any statement, representation, warranty, understanding, promise or assurance (whether negligently or innocently made) of any person (whether party to this Licence or not) other than as expressly set out in this Licence. Nothing in this Clause 6.3 shall operate to limit or exclude any liability for fraud. 
	6.4 A person who is not a party to this Licence has no rights under the Contracts (Rights of Third Parties) Act 1999 to enforce or enjoy the benefit of any term of this Licence. 
	6.5 This Licence will be governed by and construed in accordance with English law and we both agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English courts. 

	4 Earth Intelligence Ltd
	ATTN: LEGAL DEPARTMENT
	Unit 1 Kings Court,
	Little King Street,
	Bristol,
	City of Bristol,
	BS1 5EH,
	UK
	Email: info@4earthintelligence.com</gco:CharacterString>
			  </useLimitation>
          <accessConstraints>
            <MD_RestrictionCode codeList="http://www.fgdc.gov/nap/metadata/register/codelists.html#napMD_RestrictionCode" codeListValue="licenseEndUser" codeSpace="ISOTC211/19139/NAP">licenseEndUser</MD_RestrictionCode>
          </accessConstraints>
          <useConstraints>
            <MD_RestrictionCode codeList="http://www.fgdc.gov/nap/metadata/register/codelists.html#napMD_RestrictionCode" codeListValue="licenseEndUser" codeSpace="ISOTC211/19139/NAP">licenseEndUser</MD_RestrictionCode>
          </useConstraints>
        </MD_LegalConstraints>
      </resourceConstraints>
      <spatialRepresentationType>
        <MD_SpatialRepresentationTypeCode codeList="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/resources/Codelist/gmxCodelists.xml#MD_SpatialRepresentationTypeCode" codeListValue="textTable" codeSpace="ISOTC211/19115">textTable</MD_SpatialRepresentationTypeCode>
      </spatialRepresentationType>
      <spatialResolution>
        <MD_Resolution>
          <equivalentScale>
            <gco:denominator>25000</gco:denominator>
          </equivalentScale>
        </MD_Resolution>
      </spatialResolution>
      <language>
        <LanguageCode codeList="http://www.loc.gov/standards/iso639-2/php/code_list.php" codeListValue="eng" codeSpace="ISO639-2">eng</LanguageCode>
      </language>
      <characterSet>
        <MD_CharacterSetCode codeList="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/resources/Codelist/gmxCodelists.xml#MD_CharacterSetCode" codeListValue="utf8" codeSpace="ISOTC211/19115">utf8</MD_CharacterSetCode>
      </characterSet>
      <topicCategory>
        <MD_TopicCategoryCode>imageryBaseMapsEarthCover</MD_TopicCategoryCode>
      </topicCategory>
      <topicCategory>
        <MD_TopicCategoryCode>land cover</MD_TopicCategoryCode>
      </topicCategory>
      <environmentDescription>
        <gco:CharacterString> Version 6.2 (Build 9200) ; Esri ArcGIS 10.4.1.5686</gco:CharacterString>
      </environmentDescription>
      <extent>
        <EX_Extent>
          <geographicElement>
            <EX_GeographicBoundingBox>
              <extentTypeCode>
                <gco:Boolean>true</gco:Boolean>
              </extentTypeCode>
              <westBoundLongitude>
                <gco:Decimal>-0.73513282</gco:Decimal>
              </westBoundLongitude>
              <eastBoundLongitude>
                <gco:Decimal>0.11747169</gco:Decimal>
              </eastBoundLongitude>
              <southBoundLatitude>
                <gco:Decimal>51.20698011</gco:Decimal>
              </southBoundLatitude>
              <northBoundLatitude>
                <gco:Decimal>51.90661847</gco:Decimal>
              </northBoundLatitude>
            </EX_GeographicBoundingBox>
          </geographicElement>
        </EX_Extent>
      </extent>
    </MD_DataIdentification>
  </identificationInfo>
  <distributionInfo>
    <MD_Distribution>
      <distributionFormat>
        <MD_Format>
          <name>
            <gco:CharacterString>ESRI Shapefile</gco:CharacterString>
          </name>
          <version>
            <gco:CharacterString>1</gco:CharacterString>
          </version>
        </MD_Format>
      </distributionFormat>
    </MD_Distribution>
  </distributionInfo>
  <dataQualityInfo>
    <DQ_DataQuality>
      <lineage>
        <LI_Lineage>
          <statement>
            <gco:CharacterString>The data is delivered with a minimum mapping unit of 400 square meters. Land cover is delivered as an ESRI Shapefile with 2 levels of classification and area attributed.</gco:CharacterString>
          </statement>
          <source>
            <LI_Source>
              <description>
                <gco:CharacterString>Source imagery</gco:CharacterString>
              </description>
              <sourceCitation>
                <CI_Citation>
                  <title>
                    <gco:CharacterString>ESA</gco:CharacterString>
                  </title>
                  <date>
                    <CI_Date>
                      <date>
                        <gco:Date>2019-09-19T11:07:21.024Z</gco:Date>
                      </date>
                      <dateType>
                        <CI_DateTypeCode codeList="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/resources/Codelist/gmxCodelists.xml#CI_DateTypeCode" codeListValue="creation" codeSpace="ISOTC211/19115">creation</CI_DateTypeCode>
                      </dateType>
                    </CI_Date>
                  </date>
                  <identifier>
                    <MD_Identifier>
                      <code>
                        <gco:CharacterString>S2A_MSIL2A_20190919T110721_N0213_R137_T30UXB_20190919T140654</gco:CharacterString>
                      </code>
                    </MD_Identifier>
                  </identifier>
                  <citedResponsibleParty gco:nilReason="missing" />
                  <series>
                    <CI_Series>
                      <name>
                        <gco:CharacterString>Sentinel-2A</gco:CharacterString>
                      </name>
                    </CI_Series>
                  </series>
                </CI_Citation>
              </sourceCitation>
            </LI_Source>
          </source>
		  <source>
            <LI_Source>
              <description>
                <gco:CharacterString>Source imagery</gco:CharacterString>
              </description>
              <sourceCitation>
                <CI_Citation>
                  <title>
                    <gco:CharacterString>ESA</gco:CharacterString>
                  </title>
                  <date>
                    <CI_Date>
                      <date>
                        <gco:Date>2019-09-19T11:07:21.024Z</gco:Date>
                      </date>
                      <dateType>
                        <CI_DateTypeCode codeList="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/resources/Codelist/gmxCodelists.xml#CI_DateTypeCode" codeListValue="creation" codeSpace="ISOTC211/19115">creation</CI_DateTypeCode>
                      </dateType>
                    </CI_Date>
                  </date>
                  <identifier>
                    <MD_Identifier>
                      <code>
                        <gco:CharacterString>S2A_MSIL2A_20190919T110721_N0213_R137_T30UXC_20190919T140654</gco:CharacterString>
                      </code>
                    </MD_Identifier>
                  </identifier>
                  <citedResponsibleParty gco:nilReason="missing" />
                  <series>
                    <CI_Series>
                      <name>
                        <gco:CharacterString>Sentinel-2A</gco:CharacterString>
                      </name>
                    </CI_Series>
                  </series>
                </CI_Citation>
              </sourceCitation>
            </LI_Source>
          </source>
		            <source>
            <LI_Source>
              <description>
                <gco:CharacterString>Source imagery</gco:CharacterString>
              </description>
              <sourceCitation>
                <CI_Citation>
                  <title>
                    <gco:CharacterString>ESA</gco:CharacterString>
                  </title>
                  <date>
                    <CI_Date>
                      <date>
                        <gco:Date>2019-09-19T11:07:21.024Z</gco:Date>
                      </date>
                      <dateType>
                        <CI_DateTypeCode codeList="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/resources/Codelist/gmxCodelists.xml#CI_DateTypeCode" codeListValue="creation" codeSpace="ISOTC211/19115">creation</CI_DateTypeCode>
                      </dateType>
                    </CI_Date>
                  </date>
                  <identifier>
                    <MD_Identifier>
                      <code>
                        <gco:CharacterString>S2A_MSIL2A_20190919T110721_N0213_R137_T30UYB_20190919T140654</gco:CharacterString>
                      </code>
                    </MD_Identifier>
                  </identifier>
                  <citedResponsibleParty gco:nilReason="missing" />
                  <series>
                    <CI_Series>
                      <name>
                        <gco:CharacterString>Sentinel-2A</gco:CharacterString>
                      </name>
                    </CI_Series>
                  </series>
                </CI_Citation>
              </sourceCitation>
            </LI_Source>
          </source>
		            <source>
            <LI_Source>
              <description>
                <gco:CharacterString>Source imagery</gco:CharacterString>
              </description>
              <sourceCitation>
                <CI_Citation>
                  <title>
                    <gco:CharacterString>ESA</gco:CharacterString>
                  </title>
                  <date>
                    <CI_Date>
                      <date>
                        <gco:Date>2019-09-19T11:07:21.024Z</gco:Date>
                      </date>
                      <dateType>
                        <CI_DateTypeCode codeList="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/resources/Codelist/gmxCodelists.xml#CI_DateTypeCode" codeListValue="creation" codeSpace="ISOTC211/19115">creation</CI_DateTypeCode>
                      </dateType>
                    </CI_Date>
                  </date>
                  <identifier>
                    <MD_Identifier>
                      <code>
                        <gco:CharacterString>S2A_MSIL2A_20190919T110721_N0213_R137_T30UYC_20190919T140654</gco:CharacterString>
                      </code>
                    </MD_Identifier>
                  </identifier>
                  <citedResponsibleParty gco:nilReason="missing" />
                  <series>
                    <CI_Series>
                      <name>
                        <gco:CharacterString>Sentinel-2A</gco:CharacterString>
                      </name>
                    </CI_Series>
                  </series>
                </CI_Citation>
              </sourceCitation>
            </LI_Source>
          </source>
        </LI_Lineage>
      </lineage>
    </DQ_DataQuality>
  </dataQualityInfo>
  <metadataMaintenance>
    <MD_MaintenanceInformation>
      <maintenanceAndUpdateFrequency>
        <MD_MaintenanceFrequencyCode codeList="http://www.isotc211.org/2005/resources/Codelist/gmxCodelists.xml#MD_MaintenanceFrequencyCode" codeListValue="notPlanned" codeSpace="ISOTC211/19115">notPlanned</MD_MaintenanceFrequencyCode>
      </maintenanceAndUpdateFrequency>
    </MD_MaintenanceInformation>
  </metadataMaintenance>
</MD_Metadata>